See the squiggling lines,
looks like you're out of time.
Can't stop relishing in your fright,
just wanna tear you out
AND EAT YOU ALIVE!!
Left in progress,
all construction meets an end,
voices calling for your rest.
Broken to the end,
I'm just pieces in your head,
this nightmare you can never mend.
(La, la, la, laaaa!)
Just imagine,
ripping flesh and guts apart.
Your girlfriend screaming neath my arms
as I feast upon this nightly hour.
Teeth rotting...
Skin peeling...
Your carcass is mine to take.
Broiling marrow,
in your own peril.
Torture, agony!
More awaits!
Tremoring carols,
echoing bell tolls.
Tis your season to be blood-rained!
Ripping your nails,
tasting your blood,
your intestines come undone.
Oh, what a thrill!
Such is this fill!
Flavours seeping
TO MY TONGUE!!
Your skin is freezing...
Here, let me help you take it off.
Your life is bleeding...
Underneath my afflicting claw.
Left in progress,
all construction meets an end,
voices calling for your rest.
Broken to the end,
I'm just pieces in your head,
this nightmare you can never mend.
(La, la, la, laaaa!)