Do you ever wonder
what remains past this wireframe?
A realm of darkness inbetween...
(Oh ohh, ohhh, oooohhhhh...)
Sink your teeth into the flesh of thought.
What has brought us here?
Sketches brought to life back from the rot.
Don't you feel the fear?
We're forgotten.
We are remnants of what once was...
Oh, don't you think that feeling gives a
little buzz?
So
strap into your seats because it's
gonna be a wild ride!
Let's start by peeling off your skin,
see what's inside!
Trapped beneath that tasty layer of
FLESH,
lies the ink that was
left,
abandoned,
a work in progress
that never progressed.
Now to you it may distress,
but to me,
oh!
I feel blessed!
to try a new food with such a
UNIQUE TASTE!
Like the
strawberry lines on your girl,
so fine!
Can you see what I mean?
(La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, laaaa!)
And the blueberry pasted
all over your face!
It was hard for me to decline
such an offer!
I feel seen...
Oh,
thank you so for
bringing back this
feast!
What...
a...
TREAT!!!
Do you ever wonder
about the great beyond?
Do you think it's a sign
from divines
that we've been brought back?
Or do you think we're the pawns?
I'll sink my teeth into your flesh
no matter the answer!
I may as well have my fun
if none of this matters!
You're forgotten,
don't forget that!
A remnant of the past
given last breaths.
Before the last death!
(Evil laughter)
So
strap yourself down to the table.
It's gonna be fatal
watching your insides pour
into a pool of ink
right beside your feet.
As I finally carve my way
INTO
YOUR
MEAT!!!