Hold her tight yeah...
Eyes her thighs yeah...
Be worth it!
Show she's worth it!
I don't mean no disrespect,
but there's something about her
that I can't let go..
Baby you know that I love you,
even though my balls are blue.
I wanna spend my life with her,
even if her dad is evil,
or some shit.
Now spit it like this,
we getting freaky on a Friday night yeah!
I just want to hold her tight yeah,
her hair, her eyes, her thighs yeah.
If I die it'll all be worth it,
just to get a chance to show she's worth it!
I just want to hold her tight yeah,
her hair, her eyes, her thighs yeah.
If I die it'll all be worth it,
just to get a chance to show she's worth it!
There's something about her I can't let go...
Even though he look like a demon,
hold my blue nuts as I battle for the taken.
So I got one shot.
Learn to spit real hot!
And it might just go like
this!